<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Values Visualizer</string>
    <string name="discover_your_values">Discover Your Values</string>
    <string name="discover_your_values_text">Values can explain our behavior and attitudes. One of the reasons why we may be satisfied with one employer but feel uncomfortable with another employer could be hidden within our values. Understanding our own personal values may help navigate professional development at a suitable company.</string>
    <string name="identify_employers_values">Identify Your Employer\'s Values</string>
    <string name="identify_employers_values_text">Companies differ by their corporate cultures which are usually conveyed by corporate values statements. Yet, the real sense of a corporate culture at a particular company may be captured through subjective personal feel. This perception we might get at informational/job interviews and while networking with professionals from a particular company</string>
    <string name="take_self_eval">Survey My Values</string>
    <string name="take_employer_eval">Survey Employer\'s Values</string>
    <string name="view_results">View Results</string>
    <string name="logo">Brought to you by Career Changeover</string>

    <string name="personal_survey_statement">As a guiding principle in my life, this value is... </string>
    <string name="employer_survey_statement">As a business guiding principle for the company, this value is... </string>
    <string name="values">Value Statement</string>
    <string name="explanation">Explanation</string>
    <string name="not_important">Not Important</string>
    <string name="important">Important</string>
    <string name="very_important">Very Important</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>

    <string name="disclaimer">DISCLAIMER:</string>
    <string name="disclaimer_text">The information provided in this application is for educational and entertainment purposes only. The survey results are not intended to diagnose any disease or conditions, and may not be used by health care professionals to recommend a treatment. </string>
    <string name="accept">I Accept</string>
    <string name="disclaimer_check_box">Do Not Show Again</string>

    <string name="results">Results</string>
    <string name="table_header_dimension">Dimension</string>
    <string name="table_header_personal_score">Personal Score</string>
    <string name="table_header_employer_score">Employer Score</string>
    <string name="both">Both</string>
    <string name="personal_only">Personal Only</string>
    <string name="employer_only">Employer Only</string>

    <string-array name="dimensionMotivationalGoals">
        <item>Restraint of actions that could upset others or violate societal norms</item>
        <item>Respect, commitment and acceptance of the customs and ideas originating from one’s culture/religion</item>
        <item>Preservation and enhancement of the welfare of close people</item>
        <item>Understanding, tolerance, appreciation and protection for the welfare of all people and nature</item>
        <item>Independent thought and action</item>
        <item>Excitement, novelty and challenge</item>
        <item>Gratification for oneself</item>
        <item>Personal success through demonstration of competence according to social standards</item>
        <item>Attainment of prestige, control over people and resources</item>
        <item>Safety, harmony and stability of the society, relationships and the self</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="title_activity_tabbed">TabbedActivity</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>

</resources>
